This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
The Battle of Marineford ended with a Navy victory.
Unable to save Ace's life, Luffy fell into despair.
But this is a story from another time.
Ten years ago when the brothers ran wild with dreams of a world full of adventure.
To the sea someday!
The Pledge of the Three Brats!
Ah, here I go!
All right, gum gum!
And pistol!
Ah!
Would you pull it together already?
Why do all your moves suck so much, huh?
That's one for Ace!
Ah!
Still too weak!
I can't stop till I'm stronger than Ace!
Till I'm the strongest in the world!
Ah!
I guess that's two wins for me.
Damn it!
It's always so close when they fight!
What's the deal?
Zabo! You and me, let's do this!
Last chance to turn back.
This is gonna hurt, you know.
Gum gum shield!
Not this again.
Here it goes!
What, did he think I'm just gonna run into him?
This should be fun!
No, that's cheating! Stop it!
Just give it up with the rubber crap.
Or at least learn to fight like a normal person first.
No way!
I was so close, just you wait, it's gonna be awesome when I get it right!
Come on, one more try!
Sorry man, you know the rules, a hundred matches a day.
You can try it tomorrow.
Luffy lost 50 times to both of us.
Me versus Ace looks like 24 to 26.
Lost by two points.
So close!
You just win because you're older!
I'm telling you, when I turn 10, I'm gonna kick your butt!
You do realize we'll be 13 then, right?
Anyway, let's go look for something to eat.
That looks yummy.
I can eat crocodile every day!
Okay, but make sure he doesn't eat you this time.
You're lucky you got swallowed whole before.
Better safe than sorry, huh?
You can't swim, so stay up here and watch.
Crocodile me!
If you don't die, I'm so gonna kill you!
The harsh environment of Mount Corvo made the three boys grow stronger each day.
To the north of their forest playground,
the dirty dealings of Grey Terminal continued as usual.
And even further north than that, there was a city with a solid stone wall,
handily keeping the nearby criminals at arm's length.
The only entrance from the junkyard below is called the Great Gate.
Twice a day, mountains of discarded trash from all over the country
are carried through it and dumped into Grey Terminal.
Here it comes!
Let's go!
Treasure hunting time!
From time to time, residents of Grey Terminal will enter the city
to sell what they call recycled goods.
Hey, wait!
What's in that package?
Crocodile skin.
Want it?
What?
Go ahead!
Beyond the Great Gate is a boulevard
through which everyone entering the city must pass.
It leads to Edge Town.
Edge Town, populated by thugs and criminals,
lacks the refinement seen in the rest of the city.
off camps where there.
Let's go, buddy.
More açık from the solid buyers.
Goodbye, buddy.
Chic calm, nice, Suspense.
Uh, you're dead!
Gotta pick your targets more carefully.
You might get more than you bargained for.
Oh, damn it, not them!
Look out!
No mercy!
All right!
In the middle of the city, another stone wall reaches to the skies.
This one encloses Hightown, which separates those with noble blood from their lesser neighbors.
This is the shining jewel of the Goa kingdom.
Said to be the most beautiful country in all of the East Blue, not a hint of trash can be found on its streets.
Windmill Village can make no such claim.
And although it's technically a part of the Goa kingdom, the fact is often swept under the rug by its more wealthy inhabitants.
I told you they'd love that crocodile skin.
Our pirate savings are really piling up.
Fine, but I'm hungry.
Hold on, we're almost there.
I hear this place has the best ramen noodles you've ever tasted.
Well, that's not saying much.
I've never even heard of this stuff.
We'll eat dirt at this point.
Just hurry!
We're here.
Hello, may I help you?
Oh, my goodness, this will not do, sir.
Forgive my bluntness, but we simply do not serve your kind.
The VIP room, please.
But that mark, it can't be.
Please excuse my impertinence, sir.
We would be honored to have a noble such as yourself grace our establishment.
Give me but a moment and I'll gladly prepare a room.
That's pretty handy.
Where did you get that thing?
Oh, uh...
Yeah, it's weird.
I found it lying on the street.
Three bowls of ramen.
Thank you for waiting.
Enjoy your meal.
So this is ramen, huh?
Whoa, looks good.
Well, eat it already.
Check the words right out of my mouth.
Seconds, please!
We require seconds.
Three more bowls.
Pooh's taste!
Yes, sir.
On the way!
Three more!
Yes, sir!
Right, just a moment!
Roar!
May I come in?
Ah!
You might want to see this!
Are you sure?
Sir, I think we need to talk.
They found us out!
Yeah, look it!
It's a dine and dash!
Catch those criminals!
Wow, ramen sure is good!
I know, right?
Worth it!
Criminals?
They're just kids!
Dammit, how did those little pets sneak through the gate again?
I've had enough of their antics for a lifetime!
Don't let them get away!
I don't care if they're kids!
They belong in a damn jail!
Did they realize they were on the fourth floor?
Because that is a long fall!
The window is a mess, but we lost 26 bowls of ramen, too!
Sir, look at this!
Those kids left a weird note!
Ah!
What is a treasure tab?
Sabo!
Oh?
Wait!
Sabo?
I can't believe it's him!
Please come back!
It's you!
You're alive!
Let's go home!
The hell is this?
Are you friends with that old dude, Sabo?
I think he knows you!
He's confusing me with someone else, that's all!
Sabo?
No!
Sabo!
Come back!
You're wrong. I'm not hiding anything.
Oh, that's cool then.
Come on, how stupid can you get? He's full of it.
Damn it, Szabo. We can't keep secrets from each other.
So, talk.
There's nothing for me to tell you.
You trying to pick a fight with me? Spit it out already.
Okay, okay, just stop killing me.
The son of a noble.
Who is?
I am.
Hmm. So?
If you don't care, then why didn't you ask me?
The truth is, both my parents are still alive.
So yeah, I'm not an orphan.
That means I lied about growing up in Grey Terminal, too.
And that guy who was calling out to me?
That was my dad.
I'm sorry. I know I've been lying to you guys for a long time now.
Well, he said he's sorry, so we gotta forgive him.
I'm not forgiving anyone till I hear the whole story.
If you're really from a noble family, why would you want to live in some crappy junk heap?
Because I ran away from home, that's why.
You understand, don't you, Sabo?
A noble must be a gentleman.
Educated, well-mannered, and wise.
And then, when you're older, you can marry a girl from a royal family.
That will make Mommy and Daddy very happy.
Of course, I'm sure you'll be very happy, too.
All I have to do is study and meet the right girl?
Then everybody will be happy as long as we live?
Hmm. If you work very hard at it.
Good boy, Sabo.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
That's ridiculous!
What do you mean the cargo ship's sunk?
I don't give a damn about the crew!
Most supplies weren't cheap, you know!
Someone will pay for this!
Hello? Hello?
Calic?
I cannot afford this.
What a mess.
Hey, Dad.
Look at this.
I drew it for you.
Your father is having a trying day at work, Sabo.
If you have time to draw this, you have time to study.
Hey, you!
I'm from the royal family.
And that means you have to do everything I say.
Carry me back to my house.
How dare you!
I'm related to the king, and I want to piggyback ride right now!
Stop! Get off of me!
Huh?
Ugh!
You nobles think you're so hot, don't you?
This ought to teach you!
My son has royal blood!
I won't stand for you spilling it on the pavement, you old!
Sabo!
Tell me you didn't get in a fight with this boy from the royal family!
Well, kind of.
I mean, he attacked me with this scary knife, so...
My son can be such a little beast.
I blame myself.
I do hope you aren't hurt!
It's terrible, I know.
Please forgive us.
I assure you, he will be punished severely for this.
I'll do anything I can to make things right.
Shall we go to the doctor to make sure your son isn't injured?
Then I realized, they love their money, their property, their status, but not their son.
If I couldn't marry into a royal family, I was useless to them.
They tried to teach me culture and literature and all that stuff.
But I guess I didn't learn fast enough, because they were always arguing and getting mad.
That family had no place for someone like me.
I know you guys have it worse, but even if I had parents, I was still alone.
I heard that you've been sneaking out behind my back, going goodness knows where.
I shouldn't have to tell you this, but stay away from Grey Terminal if you know it's good for you.
We nobles are privileged to live in Hightown with the king and his family.
It's a life the people down there can only dream of.
By the same token, you do not belong in their world.
What, you again?
I don't know where your parents are, but someone's going to string you up by those suspenders of yours if you keep hanging around here.
Please tell me another story!
I want to hear about all the different countries you've seen, and about all your adventures on the high seas!
Huh?
You're a weird kid, but I'll give you a pass.
Yeah, take a seat.
Okay!
Well, at least the people in Grey Terminal know what it means to be free.
If the nobles in Hightown didn't spend their whole lives licking the boots of the royal family,
maybe they'd look up and see that there's more to the world.
Man, I had no idea.
Ace, Luffy, listen!
The three of us, we're going to leave this country.
We're going to sail the seas and see the world.
And once I've done it all, I'm going to write a book for kids like me!
Because studying is fun when you're learning about adventure, and we're going to have lots of them!
We're going to be pirates!
You don't got to tell me. I'm going to be a pirate anyway.
I'll be so tough that all the other pirates and all the marines will bow at my feet.
Everyone in the world will know my name.
That's going to be the legacy I leave behind when I die.
I don't care if people hate me.
I don't care if they wish I'd never been born.
But they won't ignore me.
That's what it means to be strong, to be a great pirate.
I won't ever lose, and I won't ever run away.
Who cares if the world fears me or respects me or whatever?
I'm going to be a legend.
Then I know what I'm going to be, too!
The King of the Pirates!
You dork. Just got to try and show me up, don't you?
I don't know if you'll be a king or not, but you're going to do something crazy.
I know that much for sure.
We all want to be pirates together, though, don't we?
We're only saving for one ship, but what if all three of us want to be captain?
Damn it, I never thought of that.
Sabo, I always figured you'd be the navigator on my ship.
You guys are welcome to join my crew.
No thanks!
But I was nice about it and everything.
Also, I'm going to be the king, so I've got to be the boss.
Who wants a crybaby captain?
Not me.
Me neither.
What did you call me?
Whatever.
You gave up.
Man, you're always good for a laugh, aren't you?
Well, we'll figure it out when the time comes.
Maybe we'll leave on one ship and maybe we'll leave on three.
Oh, you stole that from Dadan, huh?
Let me tell you guys a secret.
All it takes to become brothers is to share some sake.
Whoa, really?
That's so cool!
We may sail in different seas, with different crews on different ships.
But wherever we go and whatever adventures we have,
we'll always be brothers and nobody can take that away.
From now on, we're honest-to-goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
Brothers!
The antics of Luffy and his friends began to test Dadan's patience,
and when Garp unexpectedly pays a visit, the situation becomes desperate.
Determined to stay on their path,
the three boys must learn to stand on their own two feet.
On the next, One Piece.
Leaving the Dadan family for good?
The kids' hideout has been built.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!